Akshay Patidar

akshayp604@gmail.com 9685596455 Skype- akshayp604 Narayangarh, Madhya Pradesh

Summary

I am a dedicated hard working team player with experience and excellent knowledge on cutting edge up-to-date web development technologies Angular JS, Node JS, Express JS, MongoDB seeking a web developer role in your company. I am willing to utilize my 2.7+ years of experience as MEAN Stack web developer and excellent creative skills for your company achieve its goals.

Experience

MEAN Stack Developer

Covetus Technologies PVT. LTD. • Indore, Madhya Pradesh 06/2019 - Present

Software Programmer

Promatics Technologies • Ludhiana, Punjab 11/2018 - 06/2019

Projects

Covetus Technologies

MEAN Stack Developer · Indore, Madhya Pradesh

· Project: The Cloud Health

Duration From: Oct, 2019 to May 2020

Functional Area: Creation of Frontend Web Application.

Description: TCH is a web App developed in Angular 8+ and .Net. It has 4 different modules for a Hospital like Super admin, Surgery, Physician, and Patient. The 1st one for Super Admin they can manage Surgery and Physicain, In Surgery module where patient come form physician and attend the surgery, In physicain module they register the patient and send it to surgery, in last Patient module where patient able to view and edit their information. In additional we use Twilio video chat and twilio chat between doctor and patients.

Job Profile: Designing and implementing the various business scenarios in the equirement document. Requirement gathering from client. Bug fixing and debugging for modules

Software Tools: Angular 2+, HTML, CSS, Typescript

• Project: Finoporcelain

Duration from: Oct 2020, to April, 2021

Functional Area: Creation of Frontend Web Application.

Description: Finoporcelain is a web app where user can find different type of Granite marbel form the different locations and aslo we also added the different type of filter so user can easily find what they need. In Finoporcelain user can directly book appointment as well as order sample of the product according to location.

Job Profile: Designing and implementing the various business scenarios in the equirement document. Requirement gathering from client. Bug fixing and debugging for modules.

Software Tools: Angular 2+, HTML, CSS, Typescript.

· Project: Thread

Duration from: June 2021, to Current

Functional Area: Working on Node apis mainly used for data export like creating CSV files in different part of porject.

Job Profile: Implimenting the node mircoservices apis via lambda functions with MYSQL

database

Software Tools: NodeJs, AWS

Promatics Technologies Private Limited

Software Programmer · Ludhiana, Punjab

Project: Cougar-X

Duration: 31st Oct, 2018 to 10th Jan, 2019

Functional Area: Creation of admin panel and backend.

Description: Couagr-X is a dating app where you can see each other profile and also you can chat with that person and it also shows the match percentage according to your preference. You can filter people according to you preference.

Job Profile: Design and implementation of the various reusable components like business layer components which were required in web application, developing server communication js to process request/response. Requirement gathering from client. Bug fixing and debugging for modules.

Software Tools: Angular 2+, HTML, CSS, Typescript, NodeJs

· Project: Doctm

Duration: 11th Jan, 2019 to 31st May 2019

Functional Area: Creation of frontend web application, admin panel and backend. **Description:** docTm basically a Web App developed in Angular 5+ and Nodejs. It has Six different modules for Clinic, Assistant, Pharmacy, Diagnostics and IPD. Clinic for Doctors where they can see the patients and see all the records and Analytics. In Assistant, Assistant can register the patients and get the details of the patients and send to the doctors according to doctor availability. In Pharmacy, Pharmacist can fetch the details and medicins of patients and give the medicins according to them. In Diagnosis, the Diagnosis checkup according to doctor preceptions and in last IPD the Doctor can Admit the patient and leave according to need.

Job Profile Designing and implementing the various business scenarios in the requirement document. Requirement gathering from client. Bug fixing and debugging for modules.

Software Tools: Angular 2+, HTML, CSS, Typescript, NodeJs

Some Addotional projects -

· Vegsphere, · Meet n Chill, · Cosmos Quartz, · Zippay, · jaaicom, · DentalChat

Skills

· Angular 5+

MongoDB

NodeJS

HTML

ExpressJS

MySQL

JavaScript

CSS

Education

Lovely Professional University, Phagwara

MCA from LPU with 78.80% 07/2019

Mandsaur Institute of Technolgy, Mandsuar

BCA from Vikram University, Ujjian with 71.68% 06/2017

Dashpur Vidhyalaya, Mandsaur

XII from CBSE Board with 53.80% 04/2014

Dashpur Vidhyalaya, Mandsaur

X from MP Board with 72% 04/2012

Languages

• English

• Hindi